{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "He .... very tired, he is falling asleep.",
      "choices": ["are", "is", "in", "am"],
      "answer": "is"
    },
    {
      "question": " I am going to .... a shower.",
      "choices": ["make", "wash", "take", "do"],
      "answer": "take"
    },
    {
      "question": "I can't believe you went to school .....",
      "choices": ["with your feet", "on foot", "by feet", "with walking"],
      "answer": "on foot"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is not a doctor, ....?",
      "choices": ["is him", "does he", "he is", "is he"],
      "answer": "is he"
    },
    {
      "question": "What ... those people doing?",
      "choices": ["is", "all", "are", "some"],
      "answer": "are"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am very ...., I can eat a cow.",
      "choices": ["thirsty","hungry","tired","cold"],
      "answer": "hungry"
    },
    {
      "question": "United States is a beautiful ....",
      "choices": ["city","town","continent","country"],
      "answer": "country"
    },
    {
      "question": "I think Josh is a little bit .... than you.",
      "choices": ["more tall","taller","tallest","most taller"],
      "answer": "taller"
    },
    {
      "question": "He .... got a nice house.",
      "choices": ["have"," has","is","-"],
      "answer": "has"
    },
    {
      "question": "The .... is very bad today, it is raining cats and dogs.",
      "choices": ["whether"," air","weather","temp"],
      "answer": "weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "When .... you go on a vacation? Tomorrow.",
      "choices": ["do"," did","are","will"],
      "answer": "will"
    },
    {
      "question": "How .... apples have you eaten? I have had three.",
      "choices": ["big","many","much","quantity"],
      "answer": "many"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you watch any movies .... TV?",
      "choices": ["with","on","in","above"],
      "answer": "on"
    },
    {
      "question": "Don't disturb me, I .... for an important exam.",
      "choices": ["am studying","study","studied","studying"],
      "answer": "am studying"
    },
    {
      "question": ".... you ever seen a castle?",
      "choices": ["Are","Have","Do","Did"],
      "answer": "Have"
    }
  ]
}